export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Where is the La Tomatina festival celebrated in Spain?',
      choices: ['Madrid', 'Bilbao', 'Seville', 'Valencia'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Valencia',
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the world's largest unfinished catholic church in Spain?",
      choices: ['Sagrada Família', "St. Peter's Basilica", 'Florence cathedral', 'Milan cathedral'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Sagrada Família',
    },
    {
      question: 'Casa Battló was constructed by which famous Spanish architect?',
      choices: ['Antoni Gaudí', 'Alberto Campo Baeza', 'Enric Miracles', 'Santiago Calatrava'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Antoni Gaudí',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "Goodbye" mean in Spanish?',
      choices: ['Hola', 'Por favor', 'Claro', 'Adios'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Adios',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of one of the most famous monuments of Islamic culture in Spain?',
      choices: ['Great Mosque of Samarra', 'Hassan II Mosque', 'Dome of the rock', 'Alhambra'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Alhambra',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do we call "girl" in Spanish?',
      choices: ['Niña', 'Hija', 'Mujer', 'Niño'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Niña',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which famous dance form was bestowed with the UNESCO title of Masterpiece of the Oral and Intangible heritage of humanity in 2010?',
      choices: ['Zambra', 'Bolero', 'Flamenco', 'Sardana'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Flamenco',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is one of the most famous dishes in Spain, prepared in a pan with rice?',
      choices: ['Jamon', 'Croquettes', 'Paella', 'Gazpacho'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Paella',
    },
    {
      question: 'The Plaza De España in Seville mixes elements of which of the following styles of Spanish architecture?',
      choices: ['Baroque revival', 'Renaissance revival', 'Moorish revival', 'All of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
    },
    {
      question: '____ means "Good morning" in Spanish.',
      choices: ['Buenas tardes', 'Como estas', 'Buenos dìas', 'Qué pasa'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Buenos dìas',
    },
  ],
}